Guide to the Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection, 1855-1995
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Medical Center Negatives
  - Medical Center Conferences/Symposiums (Box 37)
    - American College of Physicians, 1957 December
    - American College of Physicians, 1961
    - American College of Physicians, 1963 December
    - AOA Medical Group, 1959 May
    - Auxiliary Symposium, 1961 October
    - Auxiliary Symposium, 1961 October
    - Cancer Conference, 1964 March
    - Cancer International Conference, Dr. Beard, 1964 March
    - Clinical Managers Conference, 1963 April
    - Crippled Children Conference, 1958 February
    - Dieticians, State Meeting, 1955 April
    - Disaster Conference, 1961
    - Fallout Preparedness, 1962 February
    - Health Seminar, 1963 September
    - Heart Conference, 1956 October
    - Heart Conference, 1957 February
    - Heart Conference, 1958 February
    - Heart Conference, electrocardiograph, 1960 February
    - Hematology, Post-Grad review, symposium, speakers, 1957 March
    - Hospital Accountants Meeting, 1955 June
    - Hospital Administration, Clinton Laboratory, Oak Ridge, September 19
    - Hospital Administration Meeting, 1955 November
    - Hospital Administrators Meeting, 1955
    - Hospital Administration Institute, 1939 July 24-August 11
    - Hospital Care Meet Conference, 1965 April
    - Hospital Conference, Administrators, 1947 January 22-24
    - Hospital Meeting, 1952 October 3
    - Hyperbaric Conference, 1965 November
    - M. E. Group, Jack Tar Durham, 1963 April
    - Medical Alumni Meeting, 1950 April 27
    - Medical Conference, conferences, 1961 May
    - Medical Education Symposium, 1961 October
    - Medical Lecture Symposium, 1951 October 13
    - Medical Seminar at building dedication, 1963 November
    - Medical Symposium, 1947 April 24-26
    - Medical Symposium, 1947 April 25-26
    - Medical Symposium, speaker Dr. J. E. Moore, 1948 November 6
    - Medical Symposium, 1948 November 6
    - Medical Symposium, 1950 November 10
    - Medical Symposium, 1952 December
    - Medical Symposium, 1953 December 1
    - Medical Symposium, 1955 May
    - Meeting, 1950 October 12
    - N. C. APC Meeting, 1954 December
    - N. C. C. P. Meeting, 1952 October 2
    - Neurological Surgeons Conference, 1958 May
    - Ophthalmology Research Conference, 1962 January
    - Ortho Appliance and Limb Manufactures Assoc., identified, 1954 March 12
    - Pathology Chairmen's Conference, 1963 March
    - Pediatrics Conference, 1963 April
    - Pediatrics Seminar, 1963 October
    - Pelvic Surgeons, 1963 September
    - Planned Parenthood Conference, 1962 February
    - Psychiatry Conference, 1957 June
    - Psychiatry Conference, 1957 November
    - Psychiatry Conference, 1958 March
    - Rheumatic Conference, speakers, identified, 1958 February
    - Rheumatic Conference, 1958 March
    - S. E. Medical Conference, 1961
    - Southern Railroad Surgeons, Dr. Knight, 1964 April
    - State Coroners Meeting, 1954 November
    - Surgeons Symposium, 1951 February 8
    - Surgeons Symposium, 1951 February 8
    - Surgeons Meeting, 1957 January 6
  - Medical Center - General - A (Box 38)
    - ADDA Lab, 1967 July
    - Administration, 1950 December
    - Administration, 1951 July
    - Administration, 1955 August
    - Administration, 1957 June
    - Administration, 1973 April
    - Administration, 1972 August
    - Administration Group, 1973 August
    - Administration Group, 1976 August
    - Administration Group, 1978 August
    - Administration Group, 1981 August
    - Administration Group, 1980 March
    - Administration Assistants, new class, 1966 May
    - Administration Students, 1958 March
    - Administration Grads, 1967 May
    - Administration Grads, 1980
    - Administration Grads, 1977 July
    - Administration Grads, 1977 August
    - Administration Grads, 1965 May
    - Administration Staff
    - Administration Staff, 1959 March
    - Administration Staff, 1969 June 20
    - Administrative Interns, 1953
    - Administrative Interns, 1954 June
    - Administrative Interns, 1969 September
    - Administrative Intern, Charles Boone
    - Administrative Intern, Guy Cromwell, Jr.
    - Administrative Intern, Eric Fisher
    - Administrative Intern, Don McGrath, 1954 July
    - Administrative Intern, Mabry, Greensboro, 1954 July
    - Administrative Intern, Kirk Oglesby
    - Administrative Intern, Tom Peters, 1954 July
    - Administrative Intern, Jacob Skarupa
    - Administrative Intern, Sherwood Smith
    - Administrative Intern, William Taylor
    - Administrative Intern, William Thrash
    - Administrative Intern, Julius Waits
    - Administrative Students, 1963 May
    - Administrators
    - Administrators, 1958 November
    - Administrators, first year class, 1969 May
    - Administrators, class, 1971
    - Administrators, class, 1974 August
    - Administrators, group, 1975
    - Administrators, group at Quail Roost, 1980
    - Administrators, grads, 1956 January
    - Administrators, grads, 1979 August
    - Admission, B. B. Bird and Sam Gilmer, 1941 May
    - Admissions, 1958 January
    - Advisory Committee, 1965 June
    - Aero-physiology, 1958 November
    - Aging Center, 1968 January
    - Aging Committee, 1971 October
    - Allergy Lab, geriatric wing, 1963 February
    - Alpha Omega Alpha, 1962 June
    - Alpha Phi Omega, installation, 1955 May
    - Alumni
    - Alumni, M. B. Hunter
    - Alumni, 65th Homecoming, 1952 October
    - Alumni, Triennial Reunion, 1953 October
    - Alumni, 1953 October 22
    - Alumni Registration, homecoming, 1955 October
    - Alumni, hospital feature, Alumni Register, 1955
    - American Legion Committee, visiting, 1965
    - Amphitheatre, 1955 December
    - Amputee [see Orthopedics]
    - Anatomy, teaching by movie, 1951
    - Anatomy, TV teaching in, 1961
    - Anatomy, NSF Request, 1963 July
    - Anatomy, Department of, 1947 March 4
    - Anatomy Staff, 1962 January
    - Anesthesia Post-Grad Course, 1959 May
    - Anesthesia Feature, 1956 September
    - Anesthesiology Staff, 1962 February
    - Anesthetists, 1955 January
    - Anesthetists, 1955 October
    - Anesthetists, 1957 March
    - Anesthetists Graduate Course, 1961
    - Architect drawing, Duke North, 1988 May
    - Artificial Lung Patients, 1956 July
    - Artificial Respiration, "Annie" rescue dummy, 1962 June
    - Atomic Energy, medical, 1951 October 24
    - Audio-Visual Aid, 1957 June
    - Autopsy, story on, 1949 June
    - Auxiliary
    - Auxiliary, service medal
    - Auxiliary, Mrs. Hobgood, 1957 March
    - Auxiliary, Harper in storeroom, 1958 August
    - Auxiliary, Mrs. Ruffin, 1957 April
    - Auxiliary, June
    - Auxiliary, 1938 February
    - Auxiliary, 1941 October 5
    - Auxiliary, 1950
    - Auxiliary, 1950 March 9
    - Auxiliary, 1950 April 8
    - Auxiliary, 1950 April 17
    - Auxiliary, 1950 May 9
    - Auxiliary, 1950 June
    - Auxiliary, 1951 January 29
    - Auxiliary, 1951 January 31
    - Auxiliary, 1951 April 5
    - Auxiliary, Thanksgiving, 1951 November
    - Auxiliary, 1951 November 8
    - Auxiliary, new coffee counter, 1952 July
    - Auxiliary, Thanksgiving, 1952 November 25
    - Auxiliary, 1953 June
    - Auxiliary, Thanksgiving sale, 1953 November 24
    - Auxiliary, feature, 1954 March
    - Auxiliary, officers, 1954 May
    - Auxiliary, sales, 1954 August
    - Auxiliary, Thanksgiving sale, 1954 November
    - Auxiliary, child, 1954 December
    - Auxiliary, Santa Claus as patient, 1954 December
    - Auxiliary, pink elephant sale, 1955 February
    - Auxiliary, officers, 1955 April
    - Auxiliary, duties, 1955 April
    - Auxiliary, activities, 1955 September
    - Auxiliary, 1955 November
    - Auxiliary, reading carts, 1956 January
    - Auxiliary, new officers, 1956 April
    - Auxiliary, new cart, 1956 April
    - Auxiliary, 1956 May 6
    - Auxiliary, activities, 1957 January
    - Auxiliary, feeding patients, 1957 January
    - Auxiliary, clothing sale, 1957 February
    - Auxiliary, rummage sale, 1957 June
    - Auxiliary, cart, 1957 November
    - Auxiliary, cake sales, 1957 November
    - Auxiliary, planning circus, 1958 March
    - Auxiliary, 1958 April
    - Auxiliary, voting, Miss Popularity, 1958 May
    - Auxiliary, fair, 1958 May
    - Auxiliary, planning new coffee lounge, 1958 November
    - Auxiliary, Christmas card sale, 1958 December
    - Auxiliary, counter activity, 1959 February
    - Auxiliary, new unit formed, 1959 May
    - Auxiliary, interview, 1961
    - Auxiliary, hospital intercom, 1961
    - Auxiliary, snack bar, 1961 September
    - Auxiliary, fair, 1962 May
    - Auxiliary, Negley home, 1962 May
    - Auxiliary, intercom, 1963 November
    - Award, 30 year, 1964 November
    - Award, 30 year, 1964 November
    - Awards, hospital, 1964 December
  - Medical Center - General - B
    - Baker House, repairs for moving into, 1953 August
    - Ballistocardiogram, Dr. Carl Voyles, 1952 February 14
    - Ballistocardiogram?, 1947 October 31
    - Bed, 1958 March
    - Bed, revolving, 1956 November
    - Bed, rocking, 1953 May
    - Biochemistry, mass spectrometer, 1952 February 27
    - Biochemistry, 1953 December 18
    - Biochemistry Staff, 1960 December
    - Biochemistry Staff, 1961 December
    - Biochemistry Staff, 1962 January
    - Biochemistry Staff, 1973
    - Black Surgeons, 1989 April
    - Blood Analyzer Lab, 1959 April
    - Blood Analyzer Lab, 1964 November
    - Blood Analyzer Lab, 1962 December
    - Blood Analyzer, Dr. Thiers, 1964 August
    - Blood Awards, 1977 September
    - Blood Bank, 1941 June 20
    - Blood Bank, 1941 July
    - Blood Bank, 1953 April
    - Blood Bank, donations for, 1955 January
    - Blood Bank, technician, 1960 February
    - Blood Bank, 1962 March
    - Blood Bank, 1962 March
    - Blood Donors, students, 1943
    - Blood Donors, awards, 1978 March
    - Blood Donors, first donor, 1981 March 23
    - Blood Donors, H. Aiken giving blood, award, 1982 March
    - Blood Donors, 1984 March
    - Bloom, Claudia and Madeline, 1986 October
    - Blue Baby [see Pediatrics]
    - Bone Marrow Transplant Unit, 1988 June
    - Brace Shop [see also Physical Therapy]
    - Brace Shop, 1938 December 15
    - Brace Shop, feature, identified, 1954 February
    - Brace Shop, 1954 September
    - Brace, patient wearing arm brace, 1955 June
    - Brochure, hospital services, 1952 May 1
    - Brochure, patient's, 1958 October
    - Brochure, composite, careers, 1963 January
    - Brochure, hospital feature, 1963 July
    - Business Administration, 1964 May
    - Business Office
  - Medical Center - General - C
    - Cafeteria, ambulatory dining room, hospital, 1960
    - Cafeteria, hospital, 1963
    - Cancer, 1957 April
    - Cancer, research
    - Cancer, fire in lab, 1949 September 7
    - Cancer Award, 1951 May 7
    - Cancer Awards, 1952 June 5
    - Cancer Course, 1951 June 27
    - Cancer Drive, Jean Bennett, "Miss Duke Hospital Student Nurse," 1949 April 4
    - Cancer Drive, Bell Research labs for, 1961
    - Cancer Research, 1954 April
    - Cancer Virus, 1950 January
    - Cardiology [see Heart]
    - Cardiology, three days of
    - Catholic Nun, former doctor at hospital, 1959 March
    - Centrifuge
    - Cerebral Palsy Hospital [see also Spastic Clinic]
    - Cerebral Palsy Hospital, children at
    - Cerebral Palsy Hospital, 1952 March 27
    - Cerebral Palsy Hospital, 1952 November
    - Cerebral Palsy Hospital, 1954 September
    - Cerebral Palsy Hospital, 1964 October
    - Cerebral Palsy Hospital, kindergarten, 1954 October
    - Cerebral Palsy Hospital, Duke Research Unit, 1962 February
    - Cerebral Palsy Hospital, child, composite, 1965 January
    - Cerebral Palsy Award, Drs. Baker, Hohman, Whitefield, 1964 October
    - Cerebral Palsy Grant, 1958 September
    - Cerebral Palsy Research, Cohen-Pearce receiving check, 1959 March
    - Children's Classic
    - Children's Hospital, Civitan's lunch at, 1965 April
    - Christmas
    - Christmas, painting on window in pediatrics clinic, 1952 December 19
    - Christmas, nurse Minnie Jones, 1955 December
    - Christmas, displays, hospital, 1956 December
    - Christmas, displays, hospital, 1958
    - Christmas, decorations, hospital, 1958 December
    - Christmas, decorations, hospital, 1959 December
    - Christmas, decorations, hospital, 1960
    - Christmas, decorations, hospital, 1965 December
    - Christmas, child with presents, 1961 November
    - Christmas, hospital, 1961 December
    - Christmas, candy town, 1961 December
    - Christmas, decorations at hospital, 1962 December
    - Christmas, displays, hospital, 1963 December
    - Cinefluoroscope Machine, 1959
    - Cinefluoroscope Unit, Spock, 1960 February
  - Medical Center - General - C (cont'd) (Box 39)
    - Clinic [see Private Diagnostic Clinic]
    - Clinical Chemistry Lab, 1962?
    - Clinical Chemistry Lab, Electrolyte Analyzer for Dr. Thiers, 1961 November
    - Clinical Investigators Program, Wyngaarden, lab shots, 1960 June
    - Clown, at hospital, 1957 January
    - Clown, at hospital, 1957 January
    - Commencement, Hal Stephens, 1939 May 27
    - Commencement, Army medical graduation, 1944 September 23
    - Commencement, 1957 June
    - Commencement, 1955 June
    - Committee meeting, 1965 August
    - Community Health, group from England, 1973 April
    - Community and Family Medicine, British group, 1979 May
    - Community Health, 1980 May
    - Community Health Staff Picture, 1979 May
    - Community and Family Medical Group, 1981 April
    - Community Health, 1977 April 7
    - Community Health, Dr. Estes' staff, 1975 February
    - Community Health, staff, 1977 April 15
    - Community Health, staff, 1976 February
    - Community Health, staff, 1973 January
    - Costumes, pictures of past physician costumes given by Abbot Labs, 1958 June
    - Cystic Fibrosis, Pediatrics, 1962 May
    - Cytogenerator, McCarty in lab, Bell Building, 1961
  - Medical Center - General - D
    - Dedication, building, 1963 November
    - Dedication, new wing, Founders Day, 1957
    - Dermatology Staff, 1962 January
    - Development Advisory Committee, 1965 June
    - Dietetics, Department of, 1946 June
    - Dietetics, Department of, 1950 August
    - Dietetics, Department of, 1952 January
    - Dietetics, Department of, 1952
    - Dietetics, Department of, 1953 October
    - Dietetics, low fat cookery, 1956 October
    - Dietetics, 1958 April
    - Dietetics, 1958 May
    - Dietetics, Thanksgiving preparation, kitchen, 1959 November
    - Dietetic Interns, 1960 January
    - Dietetic Interns, 1969 August
    - Dietetics Group, 1963 March
    - Dieticians, graduation group with Mrs. Martin, 1950 January
    - Dieticians, 1950 November
    - Dieticians, 1951 June
    - Dieticians, 1955
    - Dieticians, in garden, 1956 June
    - Dieticians, 1956 October
    - Dieticians, individuals, 1957 September
    - Dieticians, 1959 March
    - Dieticians, 1962 March
    - Dieticians, 1963 December
    - Dieticians, at work, 1964 March
    - Dietary Staff, family medicine, 1981 March
    - Disaster Drill, stadium, 1958
    - Disaster Drill, 1959
    - Disaster Drill, 1959 March
    - Disaster Drill, April 1960
    - Disaster Drill, Page building, 1960 May
    - Disaster Drill, Page building, 1960 May
    - Disaster Drill, briefing, Anlyan, 1960 May
    - Disaster Drill, 1961 May
    - Disaster Drill at AROD, 1962 May
    - Disaster Drill, train wreck, 1963 May
    - Disaster Drill, tornado, 1964 May
    - Dispensary [see also Pharmacy]
    - Dispensary, public, 1939
    - Dispensary, public, "colored only line" [African-American]
    - Dukes, K, alumni register, 1961 January
    - DUPAK, 1986 February
  - Medical Center - General - E
    - EKG lab, for Intercom, 1963 April
    - EKG course, 1963 June
    - Electrocardiograph School, 1958 January
    - Electrocardiograph course, 1961
    - Electrocardiograph, post-grad courses, 1963 February
    - Electrocardiograph lab, 1963 March
    - Electroencephalograph, 1957 September
    - Electron Microscope, Drs. Gordon Sharpe and Alton Taylor, 1941 November
    - Electron Microscope, 1958 October
    - Emergency Area, new, 1967 November
    - Emergency, 1968 February
    - Emergency, night, 1960 February
    - Employees, E. Lloyd Rigsbee, Pharmacy Supervisor
    - Employees, Allison Herron, administrative assistant
    - Employees, 1954 September
    - Employees, information desk, retiring, 1959 September
    - Employees, janitor and housekeeper, 1959 February
    - Employees, employee of the year, 1962 March
    - Employees, employees of the year
    - Employees, handicapped telephone operators, 1961 December
    - Employees, types of, 1960 February
    - Employees, new staff, 1964 November
    - Employees, Ward secretary, 1964 November
    - Employees, medical secretaries, 1959 July
    - Employees, dinner, "Employ the Handicapped Week," 1957 June
    - Employees, Miss Mary Stokes, 1953 May 6
    - Employees, blind secretary, 1961 May
    - Employees, Mrs. Whetmore at desk, 1962 September
    - Employees, F. Howard, blind secretary, 1961
    - Estes', Dr. staff, 1974 February
    - Equipment, janitor's, 1960 February
    - Examining Room, 1940 August
    - Executive Board, 1972
    - Executive Committee, 1948
    - Exhibit, historical for State Medical Society Meeting, 1954 May
    - Eye [see also Ophthalmology]
    - Eye, camera, 1951 January
    - Eye, camera, 1951 January
    - Eye, camera, 1958 April
    - Eye, camera, VA Hospital, 1961 May
    - Eye, camera, VA Hospital, 1961
    - Eye, patient, Luther Mishoe, 1956 September
    - Eye, staff, 1966 September
    - Eye Center, dedication, 1973 November
    - Eye Center, staff, 1974 January
    - Eye Center, medical staff, 1975 January
    - Eye Center, plaque, Lion's Club, 1975
    - Eye Center, plaque, 1981 March
    - Eye, retina eye-tack, 1985 January
    - Eye Bank, grads, 1972 November
    - Eye Building, construction plans, identified, 1971 May
  - Medical Center - General - F
    - Faculty, medical school, 1962 April
    - Faculty, sons and daughters of, graduating, commencement, 1958
    - Faculty Club Officers, 1966 April
    - Fallout, preparation for, 1962 July
    - Fallout, lecture, 1962 October
    - Fallout, lecture, 1963 October
    - Fallout, test, 1962 November
    - Fallout, shelter exercise, 1963 May
    - Filming operation, fluothane movie, 1957 November
    - Fire Prevention Demonstration, 1962 March
    - First Aid, training, World War II, 1941 October
  - Medical Center - General - G
    - Gas Sterilizer, 1962 September
    - General Practitioners, 1951 March 3
    - Germ-making machine, 1959 July
    - Gerontology, D and T building, 1962 September
    - Gerontology, D and T unit, 1962 December
    - Gerontology, seminar, 1962 December
    - Gerontology, facilities in new building, 1963 February
    - Gerontology, aging people, 1963 March
    - Gerontology, building, 1963 November
    - Gerontology group, around conference table, 1964 September
    - Girl Scout activities, 1944
    - Glassware cleaning, 1960
  - Medical Center - General - H
    - Hart, Deryl Pavilion, dedication, 1966 November
    - Hart, Deryl Pavilion, plaque, 1967 September
    - Hart Society, 1963 November
    - Hart Surgical Society, 1961
    - Heart Association Student Tour
    - Heart Association, 1953 August
    - Heart Association, 1953 October
    - Heart Association, lecture, Drs. Sealy and Shingleton, 1954 February
    - Heart Association [American], 1957 June
    - Heart Association, visitors, 1958 January
    - Heart Association, Bob Hope for, 1964 April
    - Heart Fund, doctor and baby (Spock) for, 1958 April
    - Heart Fund, 1973 March
    - Heart Fund, 1972 November
    - Heart meeting for social service workers, 1957 February
    - Heart Institute, 1957 June
    - Heart Institute, 1957 July
    - Heart Institute, 1957 September
    - Heart Institute, 1958 March
    - Heart Institute, 1958 March
    - Heart Institute, 1958 May
    - Heart, patient, for S. C. paper, 1958 December
    - Heart, open-heart, operation, 1958 January
    - Heart, model and kid, inventor, 1958 May
    - Heart, surgery, open house for press, 1960 February
    - Heart, station, 1961 February
    - Heart, fellows, 1961
    - Heart, McIntosh lab, 1961 December
    - Heart, staff, 1962 February
    - Heart fund, 1965 February
    - Heat Exchanger, Smith, heart, lung, 1958 January
    - Heat Exchanger, Brown, 1960 May
    - Heating pad, plastic, 1958 March
    - Helicopter, bringing blood sample, 1959 August
    - Hematology Lab
    - Highland Hospital, Asheville, NC
    - Hospital, entrance, 1959 January
    - Hospital, new wing, interiors, 1957 November
    - Hospital, new wing, 1957 November
    - Hospital, photos from Medical Center Archives
    - Hospital, 1930
    - Hospital, new construction of research building, 1947 February 11
    - Hospital, new construction of wing, 1955
    - Hospital, new construction of wing, 1947 February 1
    - Hospital, interior, 1940 August
    - Hospital, at night
    - Hospital, emergency room wing, 1947 December 15
    - Hospital, wing dedication, 1963 November
    - Hospital, about 1938
    - Hospital, interior of PDC, 1940 summer
    - Hospital, interior, new wing, 1957 November
    - Hospital, circa 1928
    - Hospital, 1939
    - Hospital, 1940
    - Hospital, 1937
    - Hospital, circa 1936
    - Hospital, lobby, 1938 November 7
    - Hospital, group, 1940 July
    - Hospital, visitors committee, 1965 April
    - Hospital, board of visitors, 1969 April
    - Howland Ward [see also Pediatrics]
    - Howland Ward, Christmas party, 1941 December
    - Howland Ward, 1961
    - Howland Ward, playroom, 1961 September
    - Howland Ward, baby and parent, 1961
    - Howland Ward, 1963 March
  - Medical Center - General - H (cont'd) (Box 40)
    - Hyperbaric Chamber
    - Hyperbaric Chamber, 1963 October
    - Hyperbaric Chamber, 1963 October
    - Hyperbaric Chamber, 1964 November
    - Hyperbaric Unit, Dr. Whalen, 1964 June
    - Hyperbaric Chamber, 1965 January
    - Hyperbaric Chamber, 1968 November
    - Hyperbaric Chamber, 1975 April
    - Hyperbaric Chamber, first, drawing of, 1970 August
    - Hyperbaric Conference, visitor, Cousteau, 1965 November
    - Hyperbaric Conference, 1965 November
    - Hyperpnia, fast breathing, 1957 November
    - Hypothermia, research on dog, 1957 October
    - Hypothermia, gauges, 1959 July
    - Hypothermia and hyperthermia, Shingleton, 1961
  - Medical Center - General - I
    - Ice Plant, interior, 1947 January 28
    - Inhalation Therapy, 1961
    - Intercom, patient care technician, 1964 March
    - Interns' Houses, 1937 December 31
  - Medical Center - General - K
    - Kidney, machine and Peschel, 1958 November
    - Kidney, machine, Thompson, Dr. Howard, 1959 August
    - Kidney, machine, 1964
    - Kidney, press conference about transplants, 1964 September
    - Kidney, belt, 1966 July
    - Kidney, artificial
    - Kitchen, tray preparation, 1959 February
  - Medical Center - General - L
    - Lab, hospital, 1940 August
    - Lab, 1952 May
    - Lab, research, 1952 September
    - Lab, Bell building, 1963 December
    - Lab, doctors in, 1966 August
    - Lab, medical school, 1970 June
    - Lab, tissue, 1965 January
    - Lab, Vogel, story, 1965 April
    - Laundry, new construction, 1947 June 30
    - Lee, Obbie, Cancer Center Board of Overseers
    - Library, medical [see also Trent Collection]
    - Library, medical, 1937
    - Library, medical, librarians, 1942
    - Library, medical, librarians, 1954 May
    - Library, medical, librarians, 1959 April
    - Library, medical, librarians, 1959 May
    - Library, medical, librarians, 1963 November
    - Library, medical, Dr. Trent, 1949 March 4